[{"answer": "I certainly am, Wolf.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh, we're very excited.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, we haven't -- I haven't actually seen it, but I can tell you that, of course, in these times, when it is heated, things come out of the blue.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "But how did you feel, on a personal level, to see such an incredibly personal interview attacking your father in that way?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Do you feel that he really is genuinely a different man now to the man that he was maybe in his 30s and 40s?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "I love the way you framed that question.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Who are you targeting?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Well, I happen to be from Florida now.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "What do you think his strategy will be in Florida?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "It certainly has, and I think there's no doubt, I think it's going to be a race because Florida, you know, 10 days between now and January 31st, Piers, a lot could happen.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Everything has changed, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Yes, I think the beauty is we have 50 states that are very different.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Maybe not, though, the end of the story by a long way, because Florida is looming large in everything, isn't it?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Yes, it's absolutely true, I think there's no question that Newt Gingrich cannot beat Barack Obama.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Do you really think that?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Well, actually, this was about the second best night we could have.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Where does that leave you?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, the real interesting thing about Iowa was that we spent by far the least amount of money and, as we know, officially yesterday won it.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "It's like a domino effect, isn't it?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, let's put this in context, first of all.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "At what point do you think you would reach that moment if you had to?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Not even looking at that right now.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "If he ends up in a position where he could be a running mate to either Newt Gingrich or Mitt Romney, and I accept you're not going to throw the towel in -- he may -- he may yet go on to win it -- but would he be prepared to be a running mate to either or both of those candidates?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Well, I think, you know, it's like in the NFL, they say on any given Sunday now with -- we're down to the Final Four, these are all professionals, they've got great resumes, they know what they're doing.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What are you expecting to happen in Florida?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I'm -- yes, the stories that I'm hearing, what I'm reading is that he's not planning on endorsing.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What are you hearing?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, I think people are most of all looking to see a candidate that can defeat Barack Obama, that are thinking about supporting the Republican candidate for presidency.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Why do you think that happened?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "REITBART: We've got a situation here where Newt Gingrich, right now, before that, you had Chris Christie, Donald Trump, any candidate that goes out there and attacks the mainstream media immediately gains 20 points amongst conservatives.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Do you believe that was a -- really a turning point for dealing with that kind of baggage?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Yes, but I mean, Amy Holmes, let me bring you in here because I suppose another way of looking at this, in a White House way, is that this is all quite good for Barack Obama, because you've got the heavyweights of the Republican Party right now just taking seven lumps out of each other every two seconds, negative ad, negative ad, all this stuff accumulates and becomes, I would imagine, a rather useful punch bag for Barack Obama when he works out who the nominee is going to be, isn't it?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "He looked weak on that.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Look at Mitt Romney, reacting to, are you going to let us see your taxes?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Whether Mitt Romney wants to accept it or not, this -- the last three years was the era of the ascendancy of the Tea Party and he's done everything he can to say, well, I -- he likes to parrot Tea Party phrases and Tea Party ideas that are out there only because of the Tea Party , but he wants to distance himself from the people that were maligned by the media.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Andrew Breitbart, come in there, because that's a good point, isn't it?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, it's interesting, because we go back in his history to 1994 when he ran for the U.S. Senate against Edward Kennedy, a lot of the same issues came up, for example there were ads run by the Edward Kennedy campaign against him, saying that he was killing jobs.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Where is he going wrong in selling this message?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "There always are, Piers, and I think the problem is that the American public doesn't understand finance very well.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "I mean, there are two ways in looking at what they did, aren't there?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I think one of the big problems for him is the Occupy movement.", "docId": "120121pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Why isn't he showing more passion?", "qSentId": 529}]